<!--ID=B7267351-473F-409D-9765-754A8EBCDE05;Version=1|{"VoiceNameToIdMapItems":[{"Id":"27e2f1c8-cfe0-4324-88e2-cd0bafeffe1b","Name":"Microsoft Server Speech Text to Speech Voice (en-US, AriaNeural)","ShortName":"en-US-AriaNeural","Locale":"en-US","VoiceType":"StandardVoice"}]}-->
<!--ID=5B95B1CC-2C7B-494F-B746-CF22A0E779B7;Version=1|{"Locales":{"en-US":{"AutoApplyCustomLexiconFiles":[{}]}}}-->
<!--ID=FCB40C2B-1F9F-4C26-B1A1-CF8E67BE07D1;Version=1|{"Files":{}}-->
<speak xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xmlns:mstts="http://www.w3.org/2001/mstts" xmlns:emo="http://www.w3.org/2009/10/emotionml" version="1.0" xml:lang="en-US"><voice name="en-US-SaraNeural"><s /><mstts:express-as style="whispering"><prosody rate="-20.00%">Once upon a time, in a faraway land, there was a magical forest. The trees were tall and green, the flowers were bright and colorful, and the animals were friendly and kind. The forest was home to many creatures, including squirrels, rabbits, birds, and deer. The animals lived in harmony and helped each other whenever they could. 
One day, a little girl named Lily was walking through the forest. She was lost and scared, and she didn't know how to get back home. Suddenly, she heard a soft voice calling her name. She turned around and saw a beautiful white unicorn standing in front of her.
The unicorn said, 'Hello, little girl. What are you doing in the forest all alone?' Lily replied, 'I'm lost. I don't know how to get back home.' The unicorn said, 'Don't worry. I'll help you find your way back home. But first, let's go on an adventure.'
The unicorn led Lily through the forest, showing her all the beautiful things it had to offer. They saw a family of rabbits playing in a meadow, a group of birds singing in the trees, and a family of deer drinking from a stream. Lily was amazed at how beautiful the forest was, and she felt happy and safe with the unicorn by her side.
As they walked, they came across a group of squirrels who were trying to build a nest. One of the squirrels had hurt its paw, and it couldn't help the others. The unicorn said, 'Let's help them.' Lily and the unicorn gathered some sticks and leaves and helped the squirrels build their nest. The squirrels were grateful, and they thanked Lily and the unicorn for their help.
After a while, Lily and the unicorn continued on their journey. They came across a clearing in the forest, where they saw a beautiful waterfall. The unicorn said, 'This is a magical waterfall. If you make a wish, it will come true.' Lily closed her eyes and made a wish. When she opened them, she saw that her wish had come true.
Finally, they arrived at the edge of the forest. Lily saw her home in the distance, and she felt happy to be back. She turned to the unicorn and said, 'Thank you for showing me the magical forest. I had so much fun.' The unicorn replied, 'You're welcome, little girl. Remember, whenever you need a friend, just come back to the magical forest. I'll always be here.'\n\nFrom that day on, Lily visited the magical forest whenever she needed a friend. She played with the animals, explored the meadows, and made many wonderful memories. And every time she left, she knew that the unicorn would be waiting for her, ready to take her on another adventure.</prosody></mstts:express-as><s /></voice></speak>